when it is hard to read the subs, check comment on line 7.
When you make a turn in the alley and enter
That kid might come out and surprise you
(I can fly and fly again)
Who was glowing white in the dark night
And sparkled in the white snow
Maybe I, maybe I still
Love you The fluttering wishes, yeah
The confession that I never made, yeah
I will visit you with the white snow
and tell you, yeah
I will tell you while looking at your eyes, yeah
The love that remains in me, yeah
I wanna give it to you now
You're still doing well, right? (X2)
You were so special, woo woo woo woo
While snowing, in between you and me
Is full of steps that wandered around you
I regret the winter night so much
When I let you go without even noticing
I want it, the love history with you
The biggest concern in my life
The solver of the lonely love
I remember, I love you dot
Who glowed my heart in white
Who melted my heart warmly
I still, I still, I still
I'm sorry The heart that I didn't get to show you, yeah
The answer that you didn't get to hear, yeah
I will visit you with the white snow
and tell you, yeah
I will tell you while looking at your eyes, yeah
The love that you gave me, yeah
I wanna give it all to you now
You're still doing well, right? (X2)
You were so special, woo woo woo woo