motion_blur(x1,y1,x2,y2,mode,t1,t2,accel)
Parameters
x1,y1 : start point
x2,y2 : end point
mode : retime mode
t1 : start add
t2 : end add
accel : animation speed
.....1: linear
.....bewteen 0 and 1 : start fast and end slow
.....greater than 1 : start slow and end fast
Every day I just can’t control
Every night the loneliness my love
Every night the loneliness is my love
Eh Eh Eh So beast in the cube
(So beast in the cube)
Can't breathe like freeze nae momi gudeoga
Can’t breathe, my body’s getting stiff like an ice (Why! Why!)
Hey dear stay here nae nuni meoleoga
Hey dear, stay here, I’m going blind (Why! Why!)
No way losing my way neon wae meoleojigiman hae
No way I'm losing my way, why are you drifting away?
Apeugi silheo nan gipeoman gan maeumeun eotteoghana
I don’t want to get hurt, but what will we do with my love-struck heart?
Nan amu maldo deullijiga anneunde
I can't hear anything
Nan amugeosdo boijiga anhneunde
I can't see anything
Oh niga naleul tteonan geunalbuteo
Oh, ever since you’ve left me
Geu mueos hana hal ssu eobsneun nainde
I can't focus on anything else
Modu meomchwosseo modu kkeuntnasseo nae modeun ge jiwojyeo ga
Everything stopped, and now it's over and my existence is fading away
Nuneul gamado nae gieog sogeseo ni moseubi heulyeo-jineunde
Even if I close my eyes, you're still fading away from my memories
Every day a shock Every night a shock
Every day I shock (shock) Every night I shock (shock)
I'm sorry jebal naege dasi dolawa jullae
I’m sorry, can you please come back to me?
Every day a shock Every night a shock