I’ve sunk so low in the sea of sadness
kanashimi no umi ni shizunda watashi
That even opening my eyes is not worth the effort
me wo akeru no mo okkuu
At this rate to what depths shall I descend
kono mama dokomademo ochite yuki
Unable to be found by a single soul?
dare ni mo mitsukerarenai no kana
Where should I turn, what should I do?
doko he mukai, nani wo sureba?
A single ray of light suddenly shines through
futo sashikomu hitosuji no hikari
If I stretch out my hand it’s as if I can reach
te wo nobaseba todokisou dakedo
But the tides carry me off and I lose it
nami ni sarawarete miushinatta
What in the world could that have been?
are wa ittai nan datta no kana
So warm and dazzling it was
atatakakute mabushikatta no
Who was the liar unconsciously giving off that bioluminescence?
muishiki no kauntaairumineeshon usotsuki wa dare?