Just wanna think about
I wanna think about
The hesitations I'm tired of it (Oh oh oh oh)
The waiting, it's hard for me (Oh oh oh oh)
What should I do ? What should I do ?
I hate for not noticing
Hurry and just tell me
It's you I love, My love
It's you I love, I, It's you I love, I, It's you I love, My Love
It's you I love, My love (I wanna think about)
It's you I love , My love (Just wanna think about)
It's you I love, I, It's you I love, I, It's you I love, My Love
Just wanna think about
I wanna think about
You did well taking my heart (Oh oh oh oh)
That's not different from making a confession (Oh oh oh oh)
What should I do ? What should I do ?
I hate for not noticing
Hurry and just tell me
I love thee (My love)
I love you, I love you, I love you, My Love
I love thee, My love (I wanna think about)
I love thee, My love (Just wanna think about)
I love you, I love you, I love you, My Love
Everybody come on everybody come on everybody come on ppappaya
I love thee (My love)
I love you, I love you, I love you, My Love
I love thee, My love (I wanna think about)
I love thee, My love (Just wanna think about)
I love you, I love you, I love you, My Love
Just wanna think about
I wanna think about