Modify the way karaoke text looks before being sung by using the style editor
Modify the way text looks after being sung by using lines 13 and 14 for Romaji and 17 and 18 for Kanji
The next line has instructions on how to use the magic_trails function.
The magic_trails function looks like this:
magic_trails(left,right,middle,t_offset,dur,fx_dur,fx_blur,tails,amplitude, m_density,s_density,delay,syl_factor)
There's a lot of parameters but only the first five are mandatory:
left: the x-position where the effect will start
right: the x-position where the effect will end (if you switch left and right the effect will just go backwards)
middle: the y-position of the axis that the trails will rotate around
t_offset: time between the start of the syllable and the start of the effect (can be negative)
dur: how long the effect lasts in milliseconds
More instructions on the next line...
The optional parameters do the following:
fx_dur: how long the sparkling trails stay behind
fx_blur: how far the sparkles can drift from their original positions
tails: the number of magic trails
amplitude: how far from the axis the trails travel
m_density: how many dots per trail
s_density: the density of the sparkles (out of 100, so s_density=30 means 30% of the trail will be converted to sparkles)
delay: the time delay between dots in the magic trails
syl_factor: controls how many times the trails rotate per unit time; closer to 0 means more rotations (can be decimal; will crash if you make it 0)
You can set the default values of all these parameters (i.e. what happens if you leave them blank) from line 5 (the variables that start with an underscore)
The parameters in magic_aura (that's the effect on the kanji) are very similar and pretty much do the same things, however all parameters are mandatory
Believe, believe, there's magic here tonight
Believe, believe!
星が瞬くこんな夜に
star star star star star star star star star star star star star s s s s s s s s s s s s s s s s
It was a very peaceful night
sore wa totemo shizuka na yoru de
それはとても静かな夜で
The sharply cold air stung my cheek
tsun to tsumetai kuuki wa hou wo sashita
つんと冷たい空気は頬をさした
Without realizing it I had my eyes fixed on you
omowazu kitto kimi wo niranda
思わずきっとキミをにらんだ
as you made a face that said,
"...boku no sei janai desu yo" tte
「…ボクのせいじゃないですよ」って
“… I didn’t do anything wrong.”
sonna kao wo shiteru
そんな顔をしてる
I felt that I would remember this moment,
nandemonai kono shunkan ga
なんでもないこの瞬間が
when nothing was happening, for the rest of my life
isshou kioku ni nokoru you na ki ga shitanda
一生記憶に残るような気がしたんだ
On such a night when the stars sparkle,
hoshi ga matataku konna yoru ni
星が瞬くこんな夜に
If I could make just one wish
negaigoto wo hitotsu
願い事をひとつ
come true, then let this time continue
kanau nara kono toki yo tsudzuke to
叶うならこの時よ続けと
As we gazed up at the same sky, I somehow felt
onaji sora wo miagenagara taisetsu na koto hodo
同じ空を見上げながら　大切な事ほど
that the most important things were right by my side
sugu soba ni aru no kamo nante omotteta
すぐそばにあるのかも　なんて思ってた